I carry high my craven flag,
my ally I'm gonna fly and let my
struggles shoot me through the sky!
It'd be a pity if we
lingered here and let our
pretty sparks of life
blend aloud and disappear?
There may be fog that even you can't
navigate If someone strong like you is lost,
then who will set me straight?
Cause when the waves
cast, my heart exists?
It's been your kindness and your strength!
That would free me from the mist.
And just like that!
We move on.
Sail to a new dawn.
Weigh anchor, ride as high as you can!
I assure I don't need anger.
I go fast as I am, yeah.
I hear you laughing like
you're numb to it all?
Well, we're dashing together!
No, we're never gonna fall, you know!
The whole world may now be my enemy?
Water swirl, but I ain't backing
down so long as I'm free!
Thought I'll give it, come
round the current with me.
All in, wake up bright and
early, making for the peak we go!
It finally happened.
Despite our best efforts,
Nika has appeared.
And two emperors of the sea
have fallen simultaneously.
We won't be able to conceal this.
Soon, the news will
spread across the world.
The timing couldn't be any worse.
We need to act now!
What of zeal?
Is it true that the island disappeared?
Yes, it walked away slowly into fog.
What does that suggest?
They aren't going to open the borders.
Guano will remain an iron-tight fortress.
Seems they gauged the
situation and changed plans.
Whoever's in charge now is no fool.
And any hope we had of sending in a
battalion has been completely dashed.
What about Nico Robin?
Can you at least bring her to us?
I will.
Hit me zero.
Jamming shit.
You've screwed up enough.
Who are you?
What do you want?
Just stay where you are.
I'm on my way to clean up your mess!
As news spreads of Kaido's defeat,
the land of Wano rejoices after facing
20 years of tyranny and suffering.
Tell me, Drake.
Are you a marine?
Or are you a pirate?
Go to hell.
Is that all you wanted?
You look like hell. You know that, right?
You thought you could spare
yourself by joining Kaido.
Oh, too bad for you.
You bet on the wrong horse.
What could I do?
Of course I bowed to Kaido.
When I saw that monster, I
knew he could crush me at will.
Kid and killer, on the other
hand, show no fear at all.
They stared death right in the eye.
Even if I'd foreseen the truth
that they would win in the end
I couldn't face them
I am a traitor and a coward
so I wasn't destined to die?
Your prediction was wrong.
Or did someone else
only have a 1 % chance?
It was me.
Oh, man, I'm starving.
Stop making a fall of me, stomach!
Everybody knows some and
I don't get hungry! Hey!
Don't take down the fire
festival decorations just yet!
Lord Momonosuke,
I mean, the Shogun, has decreed
that we'll have another celebration!
All right!
I can't wait!
There have been some changes, so
starting today, I'll be your new teacher.
Did something bad happen to Ms.
Sarahebi?
Where'd she go?
Even if she was fun, I'm afraid that
everything she taught you was wrong.
I'm going to teach you about the land of
Wano's true heroes from the very start.
The first hero
we're going to talk
about is a man named Kozuki Oden.
Before he was even a year
old, he sent his nanny flying.
When he was four, he knocked out a bear!
Goodness, that was a surprise!
To think that Lady Komurasaki, the
most beautiful woman in the land,
was Lord Oten's daughter,
and we never knew!
Saved from a burning castle by
the loyal samurai, Sir Kawamatsu!
What a wonderful tale
of courage and loyalty!
And speaking of loyal samurai,
Sir Denjiro of the Akazaya 9 disguised
himself as a Yakuza to stay by her side?
Calling himself Kyoshiro, he
protected her all those years!
Does anyone know who took
down Kaido in the end?
Yeah, it was someone named
Joy Boy from what I heard.
Apparently, he already left the country.
I wish I could have seen him.
He's a hero, just like
the God of the Blade.
You want to build temples?
Yes, ones like Ryuma's gravesite,
starting with one dedicated to Lord Odin?
on a hill overlooking the flower capital.
We'll build more near it?
one for Sir Yasui!
and then ones for each
of the other daimyo.
And after that...
For Ashida and Izo.
Huh?
Huh? Honimaru!
Ha!
Bah bah bah bah bah!
That tickles, you little rascal!
I'm so glad to see you're alive and well!
This reminds me of old times.
You'll always be our comrade.
You fought for this country, too.
When our time comes, we'll be laid
to rest right next to Izo and Ashita.
We'll bury Izo here, if that's all right.
Yeah, of course.
This is Izo's home, after all.
I'm sure that's what he would want.
It's hard to believe,
but I survived again.
Yes, it seems we did as well.
Although I'm happy to see this day,
it won't feel right if
the ones who saved us die.
My purpose has been fulfilled,
but they can do so much more.
I'm so hungry.
No, I'm not.
Momonosuke! Momonosuke!
Yamato, where are you?
It's Luffy, Taro, and Zorojuro!
Momonosuke!
Luffy, Taro, and Zorojuro are awake!
They're going to live!
You're still quite the
tomboy, it would seem.
Not that it hurts.
Ring boos!
And Meat!
I'm so happy you're awake, my friend!
Loopy!
We were so worried about you!
You're okay, and I'm so
glad! How do you feel?
Did you sleep well too soon
to drink that much food!
Come on, let the men celebrate.
It's finally time to
get this party started!
Soon, yes, but not just yet.
So don't spoil your appetite, you two.
We've been waiting for you to wake up.
The entire country has been
planning a banquet in your honor.
We shall have it today!
Hey!
Do you not know who I am?
It's me, Momonosuke!
What?!
Oh, wow!
You're all cool and grown up now!
Your new body looks pretty strong!
Must take after Odin.
Let me punch you and see. Please, no!
Oh, no, I mean...
Those brutes are bullying me!
Help me, Odin!
Make them all go away!
Grab me!
Please, have mercy.
I'm only eight years old, you know.
Not that it hurts. Right.
He's still a kid.
Yep, he's tough.
See?
He can take a hit.
Welcome to the world of
adults, Momo. Too bad.
That baby face can't
protect you now, buddy boy.
Here.
Now you look more like your father.
Even if you're a kid, don't put trace
on my head every time you see me!
You have your parents to thank
for that strong, sturdy body.
Give it a little time and you'll be the
finest Samurai in the country. I shall try.
I'll work hard
Okay, let's eat
Oh, yeah, Yamato, we should
take a bath before the banquet.
Your prayer was answered, so you're good.
Prayer? For what?
There's a custom in Wano where you make a
wish and give something
up until it comes true.
Think of it as a way to show
the gods your sincerity.
I want you two to get further,
so until that happens,
Now, I go out taking baths and eating.
That's cool.
Thanks a bunch, Yamabro.
You helped me heal right up.
So thoughtful, isn't he?
Speaking of baths, how
the heck am I so clean?
That's because I wiped you
down myself from head to toe.
I hope that pleases you.
Mosshead, I think we
need to have a talk. Huh?
Oh, yeah. Almost forgot.
But after the battle, there's a chance
I might not be in my right mind anymore.
If that happens, then kill me. What?
That's right.
I made a promise.
I crawled back from the gates of hell.
All so I could kill you, cook.
No, it worked out, actually.
Just forget it.
Well, I'm not so sure.
Kind of looks like you lost
your mind a second ago.
Because you drive me crazy,
like you would any sane person!
You're the one who crawled back from hell!
You told me to kill you!
There they go!
Okay, let's go take a bath.
Oh, you go ahead.
There's no mixed bag.
We gotta split up.
You don't have to go alone.
If you don't mind, I'd love
to accompany you. Hmm? Hmm?
All right, back time! Yeah!
Yahoo!
That's what I needed!
Hold on, Yamato, are you sure you've...
I've been waiting for this.
There's nothing better than sharing
a nice bath with your friends, huh?
Yeah, except sharing a feast, maybe.
That's this.
It's just a bath, you guys.
You don't have to be so loud.
I hope I can be as
bewitching as you someday.
It's so warm and steamy! It's funny.
We used to bathe like this all the time.
With Lord Odin and the rest.
But they're the only men I've ever
felt comfortable bathing with.
You look exactly the same as you did then.
It's strange to think
I'm older than you now.
This sure feels nice!
It's really, really nice!
Hey, did you hear?
They said the banquet is today!
Let's celebrate again!
It's the revival of the Kozuki clan!
Let all the Regents know!
Sonny's looking spiffy now.
All right, we can take
off as soon as we like.
You're looking good too, General Franky.
Whoa, can we get a giant robot too?
I wouldn't get too cozy if I were you.
We don't know what might
happen before we set sail.
I'm sure information leaked out somehow,
so the press probably
knows what happened here.
With two emperors out of the picture, we'll
be the prime candidates to replace them.
That's exactly right.
This country may isolate
us from our enemies,
but we don't know what
they're plotting now either.
I bet the bounties for
our captains went up!
That makes me feel cool,
but it's also scary!
You're right!
The bounties went up, sure enough.
Don't know who leaked the
info, though. Oh, Pooh!
Don't play dumb with us, you jackass!
We all know you leaked it!
I left the news out, but
I let some news in, too!
Check it out, yo!
Fresh off the presses, brand spanking new
bounties, as well as some familiar faces?
who have just been dubbed
emperors of the sea.
I asked where you are right now, damn it.
What do you mean, Sakazuki?
I told you I'm in the air.
The air over what, exactly?
Well, I can see the land of
Wano from here, if that helps.
Don't do anything unnecessary.
You hear me?
Riyakukyu!
I understand, boss.
You bet I do.